Alan Freed Collection ARC.0006
Library and Archives
- Series I: Financial Records [RESTRICTED], 1943-1967, undated
  - Subseries 17: United Artists Records, Inc., 1958-1959, undated
    - Memoranda, 1958 May-1959 September
      - Office Rushgram from S. Mael to Kitty, 1959 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 10)
  - Subseries 18: WNEW-TV, 1958-1959
    - Music clearance sheets, 1959 October-1959 November
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 1)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 2)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 3)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 4)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 5)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October7 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 6)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 7)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 8)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 9)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 10)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 11)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 12)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 13)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 14)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 15)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 16)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 17)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 18)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 19)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 20)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 21)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 22)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 23)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 24)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 25)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 26)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 27)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 28)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 29)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 30)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 31)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 32)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 33)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 34)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 35)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 36)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 37)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 38)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 39)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 40)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 41)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 42)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 43)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 44)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 45)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 46)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 47)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 48)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 49)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 50)
      - Alan Freed's Big Beat Party, 1959 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 33, Object 51)
    - Profit/loss statements - Alan Freed Show, 1958 June-1958 November
      - 1958 June 7-1958 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 1)
      - 1958 July 5-1958 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 2)
      - 1958 October 4-1959 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 3)
      - 1959 January 10-1959 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 4)
      - 1959 April 11-1959 July 4 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 5)
      - 1959 July 11-1959 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 6)
      - 1959 October 10-November 21 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 7)
      - Cost and profit re-cap, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 34, Object 8)
    - Scripts, 1959 October 26-1959 November 14
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 1)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 2)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 3)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 4)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 5)
      - 1959 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 6)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 7)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 8)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 9)
      - 1959 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 10)
      - 1959 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 11)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 12)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 13)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 14)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 15)
      - Alan Freed Show, 1959 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 16)
      - 1959 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 35, Object 17)
  - Subseries 21: Payees, 1959
    - List of payees, 1959 December 4
      - 1959 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 10, Object 1)
- Series II: People v. Alan Freed, 1958-1962
  Series II: People v. Alan Freed contains documents pertaining to the City of New York’s criminal case against Alan Freed for commercial bribery, including Assistant District Attorney notes, correspondence, indictments, memoranda, reports, subpoenas, and witness statements and summaries. Files are arranged alphabetically by document type and then chronologically.
  - Admissions as to defendant’s dealings, circa 1962
    - Bernard Friedlander - United Artists (Box 1, Folder 36, Object 1-2)
    - John Halonka - Alpha Records (Box 1, Folder 36, Object 3-4)
    - Louis Klayman - Action Records (Box 1, Folder 36, Object 5-6)
  - Assistant District Attorney correspondence, 1959 November 30-1962 December 7, 1965
    - To WABC c/o Charles DeBare, 1959 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 1-2)
    - To Joseph Stone from Charles DeBare, ABC, 1959 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 3)
    - To Joseph Stone from Charles DeBare, ABC, 1960 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 4)
    - To Joseph Stone from Charles DeBare, ABC, 1960 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 5)
    - To Ernest Hammer from William J. Hartman, Federation Bank and Trust Company, 1960 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 6-7)
    - To Edward Davidowitz from William M. Kaplan, Am-Par Record Corporation, 1960 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 8-9)
    - To Edward Davidowitz from Edwin J. Kliegman, Marcum & Kliegman, 1960 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 10-11)
    - Envelope from letter to Edward Davidowitz from Edwin J. Kliegman, Marcum & Kliegman, 1960 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 12-13)
    - To Joseph Stone from: Ben F. Waple, Federal Communications Commission, 1960 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 14-16)
    - To Robert Condon from Charles A. De Bare, ABC, 1962 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 17-19)
    - To Joseph Stone from Charles A. De Bare, ABC (annotated), 1962 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 20)
    - To Joseph Stone from Stephen C. Riddleberger, ABC (annotated), 1962 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 21)
    - To District Attorney from S. Weiss, Superior Record Sales Company, Incorporated, 1962 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 22-23)
    - To Joseph Stone from William Kaplan, ABC-Paramount Records, Incorporated, 1962 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 24-25)
    - Envelope from letter to Joseph Stone from William Kaplan, ABC-Paramount Records, Incorporated, 1962 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 26-27)
    - To Guy Isnard, Ministry of the Interior, France from Richard Allan, 1962 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 28-29)
    - To Joseph Stone from Herbert S. Delgoff, Storz Broadcasting Company (annotated), 1962 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 30-31)
    - To Herbert S. Delgoff, Storz Broadcasting Company from Richard Allan, 1962 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 32)
    - To Joseph Stone from Charles A. De Bare, ABC, 1962 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 33)
    - To Joseph Stone from David A. Noebel, 1965 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 34-36)
    - Envelope from letter to Joseph Stone from David A. Noebel, 1965 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 37-38)
    - To David A. Noebel from Joseph Stone, 1965 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 37, Object 39-40)
  - Assistant District Attorney notes, 1959-1962
    - Kasandra, Paul, WABC, 1959 January 27 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 1)
    - WFS, Incorporated, 1959 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 2)
    - Brantley, John, 1959 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 3-4)
    - Hooke, Jack, Figure Music, 1959 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 5)
    - Figure Music, 1959 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 6)
    - Hoberman, Ben, WABC, 1959 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 7)
    - Korn, Bennett, Metropolitan Broadcasting Corporation, 1959 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 8)
    - Johnson, Frederic A., WINS, 1959 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 9)
    - Kasandra, Paul, WABC, 1960 January 27 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 10-11)
    - Hoberman, Bernard, WABC, 1960 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 12-14)
    - Fearnhead, Jock, KPOI, 1960 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 15)
    - Kirwan, Henry G., WINS certified public accountant, 1960 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 16)
    - Brantley, John and Alan Freed (Ace Records), 1960 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 17)
    - Brantley, John, Dateline Records, 1960 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 18-20)
    - WABC - Hoberman; Freed, 1960 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 21)
    - DeBare, Rob and Ben Hoberman, ABC, 1960 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 22)
    - Bradwell, Merle, WNEW-TV, 1960 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 23)
    - Midtown Insurance Corporation, 1961 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 24)
    - Granger, Ronnie interview notes, 1961 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 25-26)
    - Harrington (Federal Communications Commission), 1961 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 27)
    - Hoberman, 1962 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 28)
    - Kurtzah, Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1962 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 29)
    - Levy, Morris interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 30)
    - Peckover, Albert interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 31)
    - Clark, Sam interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 32)
    - Klayman, Louis, Action Records, 1962 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 33)
    - Friedlander, Bernard interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 34)
    - Luttman, Kenneth interview, 1962 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 35)
    - Michaud, Margaret M. interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 36)
    - Hoberman, Ben interview with Joseph Stone, 1962 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 37)
    - Brantley, John, Lenox Records, 1962 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 38, Object 38)
  - Assistant District Attorney notes, circa 1960
    - WINS Alan Freed artist contract (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 1)
    - Brantley, John (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 2)
    - Freed, Alan - congressional testimony (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 3)
    - Michaud, Margaret M. (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 4)
    - Clark, Dick (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 5)
    - Freed, Alan – financial (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 6)
    - Brantley, John - grand jury testimony (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 7)
    - Brantley, John (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 8)
    - Hooke, Jack and Adriane Lawner (Figure Music) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 9)
    - Levy, Morris, Roulette Records (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 10)
    - Record Firms accounting (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 11)
    - Freed, Alan - positions held by Alan Freed (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 12)
    - Hoberman - additional direct (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 13)
    - Trial brief (Alpha Records) - admissions by Alan Freed (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 14)
    - WABC - knowledge and consent (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 15)
    - Stamford Broadcasting expenses (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 16)
    - Trial brief (Superior Records) - admissions by Alan Freed (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 17)
    - Freed, Alan and M. Warren Troob (Gone Records) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 18)
    - Halonka, John (Alpha Distributors) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 19)
    - Barracuda Music checks (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 20)
    - Michaud, Margaret M., WABC (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 21)
    - Friedlander, Bernard and Edward B. Marks - music publisher (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 22)
    - Luttman, Kenneth/United Artists (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 23)
    - Weiss, Samuel/Superior Records Sales Company, Incorporated (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 24)
    - Pare, Gladys/Portem Distributing Company (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 25)
    - Blaine, Jerry (Jay-Gee and Cosnat Distributing Company) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 26)
    - Michaud, Margaret M., WABC (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 27)
    - Michaud, Margaret M. - supplement (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 28)
    - Trial brief (continued) - Samuel Weiss (Superior Records Sales, Company) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 29)
    - Bonaire Music, Barracuda Music (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 30)
    - Trial brief (Continued) - John Halouka (Alpha Records) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 31)
    - Halonka, John (Alpha Records) - admissions as to defendants' dealings (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 32)
    - Freed information (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 33)
    - Hoberman, Ben (WABC) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 34)
    - American Broadcast Company, Fox Theater (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 35)
    - WABC Radio, De Bare – council (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 36)
    - AFTRA, Bill Gallagher/Columbia, payola DJs (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 37)
    - Outline of Alan Freed - K with WQAM Miami (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 38)
    - Sandles, Jack and Herbert Dolgoff, attorney (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 39)
    - Klayman, Louis (Action Records) - admissions as to defendants' dealings (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 40)
    - Miller, Mitch (Columbia) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 41)
    - Kliegman, Edwin (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 42)
    - Freed, Alan - invoice for June (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 43)
    - United Artists (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 44)
    - Weiss, Samuel (Superior Records Sales Company, Incorporated) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 45)
    - Kutell, P. (Trade Bank) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 46)
    - Pechon (w/J.F. Brill) (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 47)
    - Seig Music payments to WINS Radio (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 48)
    - Handwritten notes on District Attorney's Office letterhead and telephone message slips (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 49-50)
    - Dates of employment (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 51-52)
    - Madden, J.J. interview (Box 1, Folder 39, Object 53-54)
  - Bosco, Elio correspondence and memorandums, 1959, 1960
    - Memorandum to Mr. Stone from E.H. Hammer re: Elio Bosco, 1959 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 40, Object 1-2)
    - Letter to foreman of the grand jury from Elio Bosco, 1960 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 40, Object 3-4)
    - Envelope from letter to foreman of the grand jury from Elio Bosco, circa 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40, Object 5-6)
    - Memorandum to Mr. Stone from E.H. Hammer, circa 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40, Object 7-9)
  - Court documents, 1960
    - Indictment, 1960 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 41, Object 1-2)
    - The People's Trial Memorandum, circa 1960 May (Box 1, Folder 41, Object 3)
  - Investigation Bureau – reports and memorandums, 1959-1962
    - Report to Assistant District Attorney Hammer from Investigator H. C. Israel, 1959 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 42, Object 1)
    - Memorandum to Thomas Fay from Edward M. Davidowitz, 1960 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 42, Object 2-4)
    - Memorandum to Assistant District Attorney Hammer from Investigator H. C. Israel (annotated), 1960 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 42, Object 5-6)
    - Memorandum to Joseph Stone from Investigator R. Johannsen, 1960 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 42, Object 7-8)
    - Memorandum to Assistant District Attorney Stone from Chief Investigator Fay (annotated), 1962 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 42, Object 9-10)
  - New York State penal law, circa 1959
    - Section 439 (Commercial Bribery Statute) (Box 1, Folder 43, Object 1)
  - Payola questionnaire, 1959 December
    - Ross, Beverly (Box 1, Folder 44, Object 1-2)
  - People v. Mel Leeds, 1961
    - Memorandum - Re: People v. Mel Leeds, 1961 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 45, Object 1)
    - Confidential memorandum - RE: interview with Mel Leeds (annotated), circa 1961 March (Box 1, Folder 45, Object 2-3)
  - Receipt of evidence, 1962
    - Loew's Theatres, Incorporated, 1962 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 46, Object 1-2)
    - Fabian Enterprises, Incorporated - receipt #1, 1962 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 46, Object 3)
    - Fabian Enterprises, Incorporated - receipt #2, 1962 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 46, Object 4)
  - Subpoenas – Criminal Court of the City of New York, 1962
    - Brantley, John, 1962 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 1)
    - Halonka, John, 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 2)
    - Hooke, Jack, 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 3)
    - Klayman, Louis, 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 4-5)
    - Kliegman, Edwin, 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 6)
    - Luttman, Kenneth, 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 7)
    - Michaud, Margaret M., 1962 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 47, Object 8)
  - Subpoenas – Grand Jury of the State of New York, 1959
    - Brantley, John, 1959 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 1)
    - Freed, Alan, 1959 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 2-3)
      Object 1 on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
    - Corey, Jill, 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 4)
    - Mayo, Sal, 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 5)
    - Nelson, Clair (Clare), 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 6)
    - Robinson, Stan, 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 7)
    - Ross, Beverly, 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 8)
    - Twitty, Conway, 1959 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 48, Object 9)
  - Summary of payments, 1958 June-1959 November 21
    - Freed, Alan (Box 1, Folder 49, Object 1-2)
  - United States Government memoranda and public notices, 1959 and 1961
    - Memorandum to Malcolm R. Wilkey, Assistant Attorney General, Criminal Division from Robert J. Rosthal, Deputy Chief, General Crimes Section, 1959 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 50, Object 1-2)
    - Memorandum to John C. Harrington, Chief, Complaints and Compliance Division from J. Philip Smith, Attorney, Compliance Branch, 1961 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 50, Object 3-4)
    - Federal Communications Commission Public Notice - G 1525: Kenneth A. Cox To Head FCC Broadcast Bureau, 1961 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 50, Object 5-6)
    - Federal Communications Commission Inter-Office Memorandum - Subject: Payloa Investigation of WINS, New York City, 1961 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 50, Object 7)
    - Federal Communications Commission Inter-Office Memorandum - Subject: Application for renewal of license of Station WINS, New York City, filed by Gotham Broadcasting Corporation (BR-211), 1961 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 50, Object 8)
  - Witness statements, 1959 August 26
    - Mulhall, Joe and John Restivo (Box 1, Folder 51, Object 1)
  - Witness summaries, 1962
    - Allan, Richard, 1962 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 1-3)
    - Blaine, Jerry, circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 4-5)
    - Friedlander, Bernard, circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 6-9)
    - Hoberman, Ben, circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 10-12)
    - Klayman, Louis, circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 13-14)
    - Michaud, Margaret M. (annotated), circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 15-18)
    - Weiss, Samuel (annotated), circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 19-20)
    - Weiss, Samuel (annotated), circa 1962 (Box 1, Folder 52, Object 21-22)
  - 1956-1958 Timeline, ca. 1959
    - 1956 - Color (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 1)
    - 1956 - History (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 2)
    - 1957 - Color (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 3)
    - 1957 - Other Color (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 4)
    - 1958 - Color (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 5)
    - 1958 - Other Color (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 6)
    - 1958 - Billboard Million Sellers, 1959 Jan 5 (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 7)
    - 1958 - Boston (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 8)
    - 1958 - Chicago (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 9)
    - 1958 - Cleveland (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 10)
    - 1958 - Detroit (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 11)
    - 1958 - Houston (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 12)
    - 1958 - Los Angeles (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 13)
    - 1958 - New Orleans (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 14)
    - 1958 - New York (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 15)
    - 1958 - Philadelphia (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 16)
    - 1958 - San Francisco (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 17)
    - 1958 - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 53, Object 18)
  - Depositions, circa 1965
    - Re: Al Huskey payola lawsuit (photocopy) (Box 2, Folder 11, Object 1)
- Series III: Publications, 1939-1992
  Series III: Publications contains materials related to Alan Freed, including magazine articles, sheet music, and yearbooks. These materials are arranged by publication type and then chronologically.
  - Articles, circa 1989
    - Dick Clark and the Scandal of 'Clarkola' [early draft pages 8-9] (Box 1, Folder 54, Object 1)
    - Dick Clark and the Scandal of 'Clarkola' (Box 1, Folder 54, Object 2)
  - Magazines, 1956-1957
    - Freed, Alan. "Alan Freed Says: I Told You So..." Down Beat, 1956 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 55, Object 1)
    - Henry, Mark. " Rock, Rock, Rock." Film Review, 1957 April (Box 1, Folder 55, Object 2)
    - Irwin, Theodore. "Rock 'n Roll 'n Alan Freed." Pageant, 1957 July (Box 1, Folder 55, Object 3)
    - Song Craze, 1957 August (Box 1, Folder 55, Object 4)
  - Magazines, 1958
    - Cool, 1958 January (Box 1, Folder 56, Object 1)
    - “The Case For and Against Rock ‘n’ Roll.” New York Herald Tribune TV and Radio Magazine, 1958 August 10-16 (Box 1, Folder 56, Object 2)
    - Behrman, Anita. “What Alan Freed Really Thinks About Rock ‘n’ Roll.” People Today, 1958 October (Box 1, Folder 56, Object 3)
    - Bolstad, Helen. "The Big Sound For 1959." TV Radio Mirror, 1958 November (Box 1, Folder 56, Object 4)
    - "Daddy of the Big Beat: Alan Freed." Hit Parader, 1958 December (Box 1, Folder 56, Object 5)
  - Magazines, 1960, 1962
    - Down Beat, 1960 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 57, Object 1)
    - "Alan Freed's Moon Dog Ball." The Cleveland Press TV Magazine, 1963 March 23-30 (Box 1, Folder 57, Object 2)